bestseniorcareonline.com 2010-03-30

# untitled

**

Pipeline Success Privacy Policy for Consumers

** **  
**Your Privacy Rights**  
**

Pipeline Success, Inc respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. As an individual who is a user of our websites, or otherwise as a user of the services provided by Pipeline Success, this Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you:

  * the information we collect about you,
  * how that information may be used,
  * with whom it may be shared,
  * and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our websites or services or transacting business with us. By using our websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

  * In General. We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and e-mail address, as well as other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our websites, the information may be sent to Pipeline Success servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.m
  * Information you provide. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our websites or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information (such as your name, home or mailing address, e-mail address, and telephone number).
  * Information from other sources. We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other businesses, business partners, contractors and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include information about your home and additional demographic information. 
  * Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our websites. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address.
  * Cookies. When you visit our websites, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our websites, to personalize your online experience, and to record information about your visit to our websites. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our websites, such as the web pages you visit, the links or advertisements you click, or the other actions you conduct while on our websites. The cookies do not store any personally identifiable information about you. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our websites.
  * Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use on our websites. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
  * Information collected by third-parties. We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. Pipeline Success and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to the Pipeline Success websites. Our websites do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows Pipeline Success and these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

Pipeline Success collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and Pipeline Success subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the “Seller”). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, “Third Party List Information”). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Pipeline Success seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Pipeline Success and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

PIPELINE SUCCESS MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN PIPELINE SUCCESS’S SOLE DISCRETION.

In general. We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your customer relationship and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, or other third parties;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other websites;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions, contests and sweepstakes;
  * enforce our terms and conditions;
  * manage our business;
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and
  * Third parties: Pipeline Success may sell or transfer individual information to third parties for any legally permissible purpose in Pipeline Success’s sole discretion.

Financial information. We may use financial information to match you with other companies, to verify your identify, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, otherwise as needed to manage our business.

WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

PIPELINE SUCCESS MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN PIPELINE SUCCESS’S SOLE DISCRETION.

Personal information. We may share all types of personal information with:

  * Authorized service providers: We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf in connection with your request for services. These service providers may include marketing and customer services firms, credit card payment processors, as well as companies that support contests, sweepstakes, surveys, or other features offered through our websites, or that provide business analysis or website support. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * Business partners: When you express interest in promotions offered through our websites or our services, we may share your expression of interest with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular offer or program, you authorize us to provide your e-mail address and other information to that business.
  * Third parties: Pipeline Success may sell or transfer individual information to third parties for any legally permissible purpose in Pipeline Success’s sole discretion.
  * Other Situations. We also may disclose your information: 
    * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
    * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

Aggregated and non-personal information. We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other customers collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our websites and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

Third-party websites. There are a number of places on our websites where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our websites, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.  
YOUR CHOICES ABOUT COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our websites.

Under our Do Not Call policy you may instruct us not to call you for marketing purposes by emailing us at privacy@pipelinesuccess.com.  We will implement your instructions within 30 days. We have policies and procedures in place and train our employees to honor your request. Please note that we may still need to call you for servicing or other non-marketing purposes.

If you do not want us to send you e-mail or postal mail for marketing purposes, you may remove your name from current and future e-mail and mailing lists by contacting us at [privacy@pipelinesuccess.com](mailto:privacy@pipelinesuccess.com)  

Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting [privacy@pipelinesuccess.com](mailto:privacy@pipelinesuccess.com). We may also grant advertising clients and email services providers’ access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the individual information collected.

YOUR OPT-OUT RIGHTS

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and or our third-party partners by not submitting your information. During registration and/or when you submit personally identifiable information to us at the Website, you have opted-in to request that we share your personal information with third parties to receive marketing communications. When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding their use and sharing of your information. As noted, we use personal information to provide promotional offers by e-mail to our Website users. We may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To opt-out from receiving any additional email communications regarding the Website, please send your request in writing via email to [privacy@pipelinesuccess.com](mailto:privacy@pipelinesuccess.com). In addition, please note that if you subsequently sign up at one of our other websites for other product or service offerings, you will need to again address any information sharing preferences that you had previously established through this Website.  

HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees and authorized third-party service providers are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. We want you to feel confident using our websites to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission’s website at [ http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm) for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

OTHER INFORMATION ABOUT OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES

Companies that collect personally identifiable information ("PII") from California residents and disclose such information to Third Parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with Third Parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your PII not be shared with Third Parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: Pipeline Success, Inc., 1 Northland Drive, Suite 215 Austin, TX 78731. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.We may provide this information in a standardized format that is not specific to you. The designated e-mail address for these requests is [privacy@pipelinesuccess.com](mailto:privacy@pipelinesuccess.com)

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Our websites are general audience sites, and we do not knowingly, and do not intend to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Individuals under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to obtain products and/or services from any of our websites. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any of our websites by visitors under eighteen (18) years of age without first obtaining the prior consent of their parent or guardian. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

VISITING OUR WEBSITES FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our websites from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our websites from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy. 

NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of our websites.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. MEDIA BREAKAWAY DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO MEDIA BREAKAWAY OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. GRAMM-LEACH-BLILEY ACT, CALIFORNIA FINANCIAL PRIVACY ACT AND VERMONT PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT NOTICE For purposes of compliance with the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Financial Modernization Act of 1999, 15 U.S.C. 6802 (the "GLB Act"), the California Financial Privacy Act, Calif. Fin. Code § 4050 et. seq. ("CFPA") and the Vermont Consumer Protection Act, 8 V.S.A. 10202 ("VCPA"), this Privacy Policy shall serve as both your initial customer relationship and annual "Privacy Notice" as defined under the GLB Act, CFPA and VCPA.

HOW TO CONTACT US 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail as follows: 

Pipeline Success, Inc  
3307 Northland Drive, Suite 215  
Austin, TX 78731  
privacy@PipelineSuccess.com

Last Updated: 1/10/2009
